Hello Gas, I want to welcome you.
They are similar because their composition, that is, the
communication that takes place,
they are doing the same kind of tax, that is, in
our
competition, 25% 25% 25% fee is based on the
reading, the one who performed well has done 7.3%
and the same
25% can be done,
so this multi-cap fund scheme basically
performs better for those who
know their own, who can maintain their risk,
they understand how much I have, so
this becomes an
option for better performance for them, now like the
fourth point is a good option, advance
[music] has done a
little knowledge, this scheme is a
better opportunity for them,
if we look at it, then
you can see here, like Nipple India
Mitti Ka Fan, I have kept Nav along with it,
this is a total of 20 streams which
Indian Municipal Tax gives in the Indian market, so
as you can see, this scheme is a
part of an equity multi-cap scheme, apart from this
scheme  The objective of this scheme is to
increase the investment of investors on this new moon day, which usually
comes from all the companies. Category money
[music] is
mode, that is, the total money till now, that is, the
total fund amount of all the participants in this is
also going to come to me and the total is
₹300 on 15/15,
which is the month of March, that is, the pricing of this mutual
fund is ₹
20.66 paise, further on 3rd April, it has increased by
26%,
midcap has increased by 44% in big cap and cash is
100% allocated, so if you see,
297% means it is in equity schemes, the remaining
3% is in text, that means you have cash in hand, if you
ever
see, for example, in HDFC Bank, its
8% is education
[music]
no investment details, so like you will have to pay
extension and expense ratio plus,
that is nothing, now you can accept it anytime, you can do it
anytime  There are two
most important areas of this
multiplier scheme. This scheme has
20 years of experience in portfolio
management.
Till now, it has been managing 10 of them for a
total of
less than 2 years. So let us now
discuss the returns. They start before 2018 and during the period of
2020,
both fall significantly. But if you
compare Mahindra Fund here,
its returns fall less.
Whereas Nifty 50 generated a return of 16% or 17%, Mahindra Mannu
Life generated a
return of 25%. And in five years, where
Nifty Fifty generated a return of 11% or 12%,
Mahindra Mannu
Live generated a
return of 13%.
If you want to see the difference in funds,
you can also see that in multi-caps.
Mahindra Mannu Live Matric is the ratio of the fund
which is
25.36%.  The
multi of 5500 which comes in the patch is
19.6% and the standard division is
7% where
Nifty is ₹500* higher,
so the comparison is good
for the fund and the exposure of flexi cap fund, as per
everyone's guidance, 25%,
25%, 24% should be allocated in red chilli and small caps
and
65% of flexi cap should be invested in equity schemes
but look here, if you understand then here
approximately 75% of them have to be invested in equity only,
so if
you understand this area then can you
tell me which category of fund will have
higher returns and which category
of fund will give good returns, so now let
us complete this video, you can
watch it on our blog area